{
"questions": [
   {
    "question": "For EIP to become a new ERC, _________________.",
    "answer": "approved by Ethereum Committee"
   },
   {
      "question": "The time taken for mining one block in Ethereum is ___________.",
      "answer": "14 seconds"
   },
   {
      "question": "How many rewards (Wei/Ether) does the miner receive for adding a block to the chain?",
      "answer": "5 ether"
   },
   {
    "question": "Ethereumâ€™s proof of Work Algorithm is ______.",
    "answer": "Ethash"
   },
   {
      "question": "_________requires lots of Electricity/Energy.",
      "answer": "Proof of Work"
   },
   {
      "question": "The native currency of Ethereum network is _________________.",
      "answer": "Ether"
   },
   {
    "question": "Ethereum tokens are created by using ____________.",
    "answer": "Smart contracts"
   },
   {
      "question": "What are Ethereum tokens?",
      "answer": "Digital asset"
   },
   {
      "question": "Which consensus algorithm is to be added in Ethereum Serenity update?",
      "answer": "Proof of Stake"
   },
   {
    "question": "What is the smallest unit of Ether?",
    "answer": "Wei"
   },
   {
      "question": "The main advantage of Ethereum over Bitcoin is __________.",
      "answer": "Smart Contracts"
   },
   {
      "question": "What is the denomination used in Ethereum?",
      "answer": "Wei"
   },
   {
    "question": "How is the ether brought into the Ethereum system?",
    "answer": "Mining"
   },
   {
      "question": "How many lower denominations does the Ether have?",
      "answer": "6"
   },
   {
      "question": "EIP stands for __________.",
      "answer": "Ethereum Improvement Proposal"
   },
   {
    "question": "Basic Structure for ERC20 Tokens is __________________.",
    "answer": "6 Functions, 2 Events, 3 Token information"
   },
   {
      "question": "ERC stands for _____________.",
      "answer": "Ethereum Request for Comments"
   },
   {
    "question": "What is the purpose of EVM?",
    "answer": "To compile and execute code"
   },
   {
      "question": "EVM stands for ___________.",
      "answer": "Ethereum Virtual Machine"
   },

   {
      "question": "Ethereum's mining process is similar to bitcoin.",
      "answer": "True"
   },
   {
    "question": "What is Ethereum?",
    "answer": "Public Blockchain"
   }
 ]
}